{
    "subject": "Miguel_Lopez-Fitzgerald",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Kay_Bennett",
    "human_readable": "Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald is married to Kay Bennett.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9645829796791077,
            "question": "Is there a known relationship between Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald and Kay Bennett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9524592757225037,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the marriage of Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald and Kay Bennett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.937433123588562,
            "question": "Name one person married to Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9343873262405396,
            "question": "Who is Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9228407144546509,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald and Kay Bennett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8761305212974548,
            "question": "To whom is Kay Bennett married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8642621636390686,
            "question": "Is Kay Bennett married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.775371789932251,
            "question": "Who is Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7719717621803284,
            "question": "What is the name of Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6437119245529175,
            "question": "Who are Kay Bennett's marital partners?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald is married to Kay Bennett.",
            "html": "yago_30236_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30236_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald?",
            "html": "yago_30236_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kay Bennett married?",
            "html": "yago_30236_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30236_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30236_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30236_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30236_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30236_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30236_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30236_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30236_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30236_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30236_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states:  \"Kay married Miguel in the July 21, 2008 episode.\"   and \"On July 21, 2008, Miguel and Kay became husband and wife.\"   ."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents suggest that Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald is indeed married to Kay Bennett, as it is mentioned multiple times throughout the text that they get married on July 21, 2008 (e.g., \"On July 21, 2008, Miguel and Kay became husband and wife.\")"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Kay married Miguel on July 21, 2008. Therefore, the statement \"Miguel Lopez-Fitzgerald is married to Kay Bennett\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}